realitysportsonline.com 2018-03-29

# Privacy Policy | Reality Sports Online

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the RealitySportsOnline.com website (the “RSO Web Site”). On some pages, you can enter information in order to sign up to become a registered user of the RSO Web Site (a “Registered User”) and/or register a league or a team for the Reality Spots Online Fantasy Platform (the “RSO Fantasy Platform”), and the types of personal information collected at these pages include:

  1. Name
  2. Address
  3. Email address
  4. Phone number
  5. Credit/Debit Card Information

On your league page, you may voluntarily enter contact information that makes it easier for league members to contact you, including:

  1. Name
  2. Email address
  3. Phone numbers (daytime, evening, fax, cell)
  4. Personal web site URL
  5. Instant messaging IDs

**Any information that is provided to a third party unaffiliated with Reality Sports Online (an “Unaffiliated Third Party”), including without limitation, League Safe, PayPal, Shopify, MailChimp, AdRoll, or any other entity, shall be provided pursuant to the Privacy Policies of such Unaffiliated Third Party, and RSO shall not be liable for any special, indirect, or consequential damages that are directly or indirectly related to the providing of such information to such Unaffiliated Third Party.**

**For the avoidance of doubt, it is understood that by visiting our website, such Unaffiliated Third Parties may at any point in time and on any webpage place cookies on users’ browsers for targeted advertising purposes. Cookies are small data files  that are served by us or an Unaffiliated Third Party and stored on your device. That data can then be used by us or an Unaffiliated Third Party to target advertising on other sites (e.g. Facebook.com) based on your online activity. If you would like instructions on how to opt out of receiving such advertisements, please visit the [DAA opt-out site](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the [NAI opt-out site](http://networkadvertising.org/choices). **

**The Way We (RSO) Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when signing up to become a Registered User or for registering for the RSO Fantasy Platform only to successfully make you a Registered User or register you for the RSO Fantasy Platform, as the case may be. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the applicable process.

We do not, in any manner, use the information voluntarily entered on your league page. It is important to realize that anyone (not just your league members) may view your personal (non-RSO) web site if defined, but the contact information you enter on your league page is only seen by league members while they are logged in.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Correct Your Information:**

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows an error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us:**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [inquiries@realitysportsonline.com](mailto:inquiries@realitysportsonline.com).
